So   So So to keep this
demo transparent, I will just wiping out
the data whatever I already have. This is
clear and reinitiating the screen, the
project andnow if I will be asking this.
What?
Lower mind, do you feel this?
In this product.
It doesn't down South. This is a guarded
system where it is not showing any kind
of hallucinating data. Now I'll be
uploading the file.
Is has been given in my local system so
it is a little bit slower. So we have
restored this much of chunks from this
PDF. These are 500 characters chunks. So
now I will be asking this question again.
'Cause these are slower models so it will
take time. Sorry about that.
So it is economic embed text model. With
previous vector 768 dimensions. So this
is what we are using and you can see
llama 3.2. This is very slow and local
model which has been installed in my
system. Now second thing is that if I
will be asking again regarding HMM.
Myself like, uh, uh.
What?
Number of years. Experience, OK.
Is trying to search in the same
documents, but as we haven't given any
kind of uh personal or resume related
information in this document so.
Which says I don't know based on
available documents. Now I'll be feeding
this. System resume.
Now it is uploaded. Now I'll be asking
the same question.
No, it can tell us clearly that Mukesh is
around 8.5 years experience senior back
end up and technically. So this was it.
Thank you.